vdict.com 2011-11-01

# Vietnamese Dictionary and Translation - Từ điển và dịch tiếng Việt

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how VDict uses and protects any information that you give VDict when you use this website.

VDict is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

VDict may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is last updated and effective from 12/30/2009.

### What we collect

VDict does not collect users' personal information on dictionary pages.

We do collect personal information in translation service order form and community registration page. However, only Name and Email address are required fields, all other fields are optional.

### Advertising 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website, including behavioral and/or multi-site advertisements. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. The advertising networks (including Google, Exponential Interactive, Inc., ValueClick Media, Burst Media) may place a 3rd party cookie on your computer, such a cookie may be used to tailor ad content both on the site you are visiting as well as other sites within that network that you may visit in the future.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) . 

In particular:

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to VDict and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  * We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>
  * Exponential Interactive, Inc. uses cookies and collects non-personally identifiable information to better customize the sort of advertisements you see. To view Exponential Exponential Interactive, Inc.'s privacy policy and opt out of receiving it's cookies please visit [Exponential](http://www.exponential.com/who-we-are/privacy-policy.jsp)

### What we do with the information we gather

For information collected by third party advertising companies please view their respective privacy policy above.

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

Personal information: Personal information on order form is used to contact customers. This information is stored on our records for 3 years.

Uploaded files: Files uploaded for translation quotes are also stored for 3 years unless otherwise requested to be destroyed by customers.

Cookies: Cookies are used to store your preferences on Vdict.com.

IP addresses: IP addressed are used for statistical purposes only.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

We reserve the rights to share traffic statistics reports with our advertising partners.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to support@vdict.com.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
